Seyed Mohammad Mousavi

Zahedan County, Sistan va Baluchestan, Iran



linkedin.com/in/smmousavisp



smmousavisp@gmail.com



+989157291339

Summary

I'm interested in artificial intelligence and specifically deep learning. I'm working with PyTorch for deep learning. I like the idea of functional programming and in my spare time, I want to learn Clojure programming language and fundamentals of functional programming. I have experience in teaching programming languages (Python and Java), Data Structures, and Theory of Languages and Automata.

Experience



Theory of Languages and Automata Teacher Assistant

University of Sistan and Baluchestan Sep 2019 - Jan 2020 (5 months)

Computer Architecture Teacher Assistant

University of Sistan and Baluchestan Sep 2019 - Jan 2020 (5 months)

Data Structures Teacher Assistant

University of Sistan and Baluchestan Jan 2019 - Jun 2019 (6 months)

Education



■ University of Sistan and Baluchestan

B.Sc, Computer Engineering 2017 - 2021 Most recent 60 credit hours GPA: 91 / 100



National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents (Sampad)

Highschool Diploma, Mathematics 2013 - 2017

Licenses & Certifications

Machine Learning with Python - Coursera Course Certificates 5V6TBJ8UVQ75

Scalable Machine Learning on Big Data using Apache Spark - Coursera Course Certificates 5N4TERYJX47F

Introduction to Deep Learning & Neural Networks with Keras - Coursera Course Certificates HBQHZEMV3FTU

Honors & Awards

- Ranked 1st in All Entries of B.Sc in Computer Engineering University of Sistan and Baluchestan 2020
- Ranked First in programming and algorithm design contest University of Sistan and Baluchestan

 Dec 2018

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • Deep Learning • Full-Stack Development • Data Structures • Web Development • Engineering • Software • C++ • Java • JavaScript